(Zack:)and Archie's married
to Betty in one
(Zack:)and Veronica
in the other.
(Zack:)Midge is even breaking
up with Moose.
(Sheldon:)No.
(Zack:)About time, right?
(Leonard:)Hey.
You guys finally chip in
for a bodyguard?
(Leonard:)Uh, no. Oh,
this is Zack.
(Leonard:)He's a friend
of ours.
(Leonard:)Zack, this is Stuart.
(Leonard:)He owns
the store.
(Zack:)Wow, lucky you.
(Stuart:)Yeah, I work
70 hours a week
(Stuart:)and average
$1.65 an hour.
(Zack:)Sweet.
(Stuart:)Is that sarcasm?
(Howard:)No, it's an indictment of the
American education system.
The Archies are over here.
(Zack:)Yippee.
(Stuart:)So are you guys coming to
my New Year's Eve costume party?
(Sheldon:)Of course.
(Sheldon:)We're coming as the
Justice League of America.
(Howard:)Switching it up from last year
(Howard:)when we came as
the Justice League of America.
(Sheldon:)To that point,
(Sheldon:)it occurs to me that we
might have an opportunity
(Sheldon:)to finally snare
Best Group Costume